# Griffen Agnello

360-281-9034 | agnellogriffen@gmail.com | Vancouver, WA https://github.com/quakeroatsgriff | www.linkedin.com/in/griffen-agnello

# **Projects**

#### Capstone – Automated Speech Recognition

 Worked with Seasalt.AI to create English and Spanish speech-to-text machine learning models. The models are trained with audio crawled from YouTube. Several Python scripts and Bash scripts were used to get the G2P model to train and predict. Learned to act as a team lead for the project.

#### Kaggle Competition – Natural Disaster Classification

Machine learning model that predicts if a tweet reports a natural disaster or not. Used scikit-learn's Count Vectorizer and Random Forest Classifier classes in Python. The model was 80.4% correct using the competition test data set.

#### Personal Web Portfolio

My personal portfolio website that includes a blog, project posts, contact info, and other
personal information about me. Uses Node.js and Express.js as the server back-end. Uses
Pug, BS5, and self-made CSS as the webpage front-end. <a href="https://griffenagnello.adaptable.app/">https://griffenagnello.adaptable.app/</a>

# **Technical Skills**

**Proficient Languages:** Python | HTML5 | CSS | Javascript | C / C++ | LaTeX | SQL | Java | Scala **Experienced With:** Scikit-learn | Git | Linux | Node.js / Express.js | Bootstrap 5 | Agile | WebGL

# **Work Experience**

## **Course Development Internship**

Aug. 2022 - Current

Lumen Learning

- Practiced professional project management in a real-world work environment.
- Programmed academic coursework questions in Lumen's Online Homework Manager (OHM).
- Applied HTML, CSS, PHP, and LaTeX knowledge to formulate questions.

#### **Computer Science Teaching Assistant**

Jan. 2022 – May 2022

Washington State University Vancouver

- Tutored students about the fundamentals of the C programming language.
- Provided insightful feedback on students' code.
- Covered topics such as pointers, arrays, recursion, and data structures.

# **Education**

### **Bachelor of Science – Computer Science**

Aug. 2021 – May 2023

Washington State University Vancouver

- Academic Honors: Magna Cum Laude
- President's Honor Roll for 3 semesters
- Coursework: Machine Learning | Artificial Intelligence | Software Engineering | Network Security | Functional Programming | Graphics | Game Design | Operating Systems | Databases

### **Associate of Science – Computer Science**

Sep. 2019 – Aug 2022

Clark College

- Cumulative GPA: 3.60
- Vice President's List Award for 5 quarters
- Coursework: Java | Data Structures | Object-Oriented Programming | Linux | Scripting | C